[theme music playing]
[gunshots]
[gun clicks, fires]
[whoosh, slashing sounds]
[machine gun fire]
[machine gun fire continues]
[single gunshot]
[rapid gunfire]
[echoing blast]
[blade whooshing]
[tense music builds]
[Julio] Lily Cruz…
We meet again.
I will make you suffer
like I am suffering right now.
If Red Dragon's daughter
really is ferocious,
then we are unstoppable together.
My mama taught me very well.
[Julio] Emilia.
Get your big behind up here.
Yes.
We have her again.
The indestructible
Lily Cruz.
[Lily] I won't let these butchers win.
As long as I'm alive, I'll always
have an ace up my sleeve.
I will not go down without a fight.
Jepoy, it's time.
We must execute Lily's plans now.
What we need is strong evidence
of the Ardientes' heinous crimes.
I saw skeletons in the woods
of San Bartolome.
Exposing the Ardientes' dastardly deeds
may be the only way to save Lily.
[man] Listen up, everyone!
The governor wants us
to head over to the plaza.
He said they will bring
Lily Cruz there and punish her
for murdering our mayor!
[crowd chanting]
Viva, Ardiente! Viva, Ardiente!
[Julio] Behold the cancer
afflicting this town.
-Lily Cruz!
-[crowd jeering]
-She killed the mayor!
-You murderer!
You deserve to be punished!
Marlon! Jepoy!
[Edna] What if Mom and Dad
are down there, Ronald?
Mom?
[Camia] Lily!
You monsters! Let her go!
[Emilia] We are going for a walk.
I'm going to escort you to hell!
We're going to call this
"The March of Sinners."
[Lily] To save Diego
and to light the hope that
the people's suffering will end,
I will do it.
[crowd jeering]
-[heavy breathing]
-[chilling music playing]
[Ronald sobs]
[Edna] Ma? Pa?
Where are my mother and father?!
Where are they?!
[chilling music playing]
[Ronald] How will we find
our parents here?!
Tell me!
I know they've been dead for years.
But to simply dump their bodies here?
They're monsters.
They desecrated our parents.
[breath quivers]
[Edna] They didn't even stop to think
that these people they killed
have a father, a mother,
a child, a sibling…
They have no regard
for human life, Ronald!
-Edna… [cries]
-[Edna whimpers]
[screams] The Ardientes are monsters!
-Monsters!
-[crying]
[Edna] What did they do to our parents?!
[hoarse screams] This isn't my child!
It's not!
[stuttering] This can't be my child!
[sobbing, wheezing]
[woman wailing]
[chilling music playing]
Friends, Mister Fernan,
gather all the residents of Ardiente.
Even the Ardiente loyalists.
Call the press so the whole world can see
the ruthlessness of the Ardientes.
-All right.
-Let's go.
Come on. Hurry.
Let's go.
[dramatic music playing]
-[foreboding music playing]
-[indistinct chatter]
Colonel.
Sir.
I am sure Diego Torillo…
will rescue his wife.
Now, it is a very stupid move on his part.
But I know he has no choice.
He'll be forced to come here.
I want you to tell all your men
that the moment they see Diego Torillo…
I want them to shoot him down
and bring his body to me.
Yes, sir.
All four walls. All four
walls on this channel.
Standing order from the Governor:
when the primary Tango arrives,
shoot to kill.
I repeat, shoot to kill. Confirm.
[in Spanish] Blood will
be paid with blood.
Blood will be paid…
with blood.
[ominous music playing]
-[whip cracking]
-[Lily groaning]
-[Lily grunts]
-You witch!
-Hit her!
-Scum!
-Murderer!
[whip cracking]
-[Emilia] You want some more?!
-[Camia crying]
-Kill her!
-Murderer!
-Lily!
-Viva Ardiente!
I AM A MURDERER
I KILLED YOUR MAYOR
[whip cracking]
-[crowd jeering]
-Oh, Lily…
Let go! Don't touch me!
-[Emilia] What?!
-[whip cracking]
Lily!
[crowd continues jeering]
[Emilia] Want more?!
-Kill her!
-Move!
-Miss Camia!
-[Camia crying]
-Miss Camia, please help Lily!
-Let us through!
-Let us through, sir!
-Miss Camia, help…
-Please, sir! Let us through!
-[Camia wailing] Lily!
-[crowd continues jeering]
-[dramatic music playing]
[man] She's a scum!
[man] That's what she deserves!
Lily…
[wailing] Please, have mercy. Stop it.
Stop hurting Lily!
She doesn't deserve this!
-Scum! Keep walking!
-Get up!
[crowd continues jeering]
[dramatic music playing]
Enough!
[Lily] If this is where it all ends,
there are only two things I'll ask for.
I want my husband, Diego, to live,
and for my mother to always be safe,
so they can continue the fight…
And that someday,
this town will finally be free
of the Ardientes.
Forgive me…
for lighting the fire
I should've extinguished myself.
[melancholic music playing]
[crowd jeering]
-Get up!
-Kill her!
-Punish her!
-[Camia crying]
-Stop torturing her!
-She deserves it!
-Don't kill her, please!
[crowd continues jeering]
My daughter!
-Kill her!
-She's a scum!
[crowd cheers]
[somber music playing]
[music fades]
[unsettling music playing]
[unsettling music intensifies]
[chilling music playing]
[Lily] If my life ends here,
please help me until my last breath
because I'm not leaving this town
without putting up a fight.
[chilling music continues playing]
[wailing]
[man] Don't come any closer.
Lily…
-Nanny?
-Lily…
[voice shaking] Lily?
[Lily] Nanny Carlotta…
[dramatic music playing]
[sobbing]
[Lily] It hurts so much.
Lily, you can do this.
I don't know if I can. [breath hitches]
I'm too weak, Nanny. [gasps]
I'm too weak to fight. [wheezes]
[crying]
-Nanny… [whimpers]
-Lily… [shushes]
Get up, Lily.
-[Lily shivering]
-Get up, my dear.
Shh.
-I can't, Nanny.
-Shh!
Keep fighting, dear. You can do it.
You can do it.
[dramatic music playing]
Dad?
Take me with you, Dad.
I'm giving up.
I give up.
No, Lily.
Keep fighting.
[crying]
Don't give up.
But it hurts so much, Dad.
[Lily sobs]
[dramatic music playing]
So, you want more, huh?!
Please stop hurting her!
[wailing] Have mercy!
[crowd jeering]
[somber music playing]
[camera shutter clicking]
[man] I can't believe they left
your mother's body here.
[camera shutter clicking]
This is my mom's rosary…
They're worse than animals!
Those Ardientes are worse than animals!
They're monsters!
Wretched monsters! [sobs]
Curse them!
[sobbing]
Now that we have proof
of the Ardiente family's crimes,
it's time for us to rise up against them
so that no citizen of Poblacion Ardiente
will ever suffer the same horrible fate
as our parents, siblings, and children.
Now is the time
for change!
Justice for our families!
And justice for the victims
of the Ardientes!
It's time for retribution!
Down with the Ardientes!
[people chanting] Down with the Ardientes!
[camera shutter clicks]
I heard they dump
anyone who goes
against the Ardientes there.
But no one's been able to confirm it,
and that's why they can still claim
that this town is crime-free.
This means Lily's been telling the truth.
That the Ardientes really did kidnap
their families and kill them.
Lily Cruz was right!
She's been fighting for justice.
You're all right.
And if we don't take action now,
Lily Cruz will end up dead
like those corpses.
And it could happen to you, me…
and everyone else.
So, we have to act now.
[woman] Right!
Let's fight for what's right.
Let's expose the truth.
-Down with the Ardientes!
-Down!
Down with the Ardientes!
Down!
[chanting continues]
Down with the Ardientes!
Emilia Ardiente-Torillo took over
Red Dragon's organization
while her mother was in hiding.
[Helena] And while I'm away,
I am entrusting my position
to my baby girl.
My baby dragon, Emilia Ardiente-Torillo.
I'm ready to expose
all the crimes she committed.
I was ordered to bomb
Lily Cruz's building.
Where's the bomb?!
-[bomb timer beeping]
-[tense music playing]
I was the chairman of the council
in the previous elections.
-[sighs] I accepted bribes…
-[camera shutter clicks]
…from Julio Ardiente
to rig the election results
so he could be elected as
governor of Poblacion Ardiente.
[Julio] Here's your fifty million pesos.
And there's an additional ten million
for helping me win this election.
I regret everything I've done.
The true winner of that election…
was Diego Torillo.
He is the true governor…
of Poblacion Ardiente.
We have intelligence reports
that will prove
that the Ardientes took over
Red Dragon's syndicate.
I was once
Emilia Ardiente's henchman.
It was Emilia Ardiente…
who had Dante Cruz poisoned and killed.
-[tires screeching]
-[loud crash]
I went insane when I realized
I was the one who gave
the poison that killed him.
My conscience has been eating me up.
Out of jealousy,
Emilia Ardiente ordered me,
to rape, kill, and bury Camia Cruz.
Because Raul, Emilia's husband
was in love with Camia.
Lily Cruz hid me abroad.
She protected me
so I could come here
and tell the whole world
about the Ardientes' evil deeds.
Let's all help Lily Cruz.
Let's all give her family justice!
Attorney, how's your case
against the Ardientes?
The provincial prosecution
has found sufficient grounds
to pursue the case against the Ardientes.
This case is definitely moving forward.
What charges will they be pressed with?
Multiple counts of murder.
Frustrated murder,
election fraud, among many others.
I too was a victim
of that wretched Ardiente family.
They killed my father.
[suspenseful music playing]
[camera shutter clicking]
-[gunshot]
-Ah!
Enough is enough.
It is game over
for the governor and his wicked daughter.
Because I have joined
Ms. Lily Cruz's fight.
Justice will be served.
And I will make sure…
that it hits them hard.
-Down with the Ardientes!
-Down!
Down! Down!
-Down with the Ardientes!
-Down!
Move!
-She deserves to die!
-Hang her!
-Hang that murderer!
-Kill Lily!
[crowd jeering]
[hoarse screams] Stop this!
[crowd continues jeering]
This woman just won't die, will she?
-Hang her!
-Kill her!
After this, hang her.
I know. I don't wanna say it, Papa, but…
your wish is always my command.
-You deserve to die!
-Go to hell!
-You killed the mayor!
-Die, Lily!
[Emilia claps]
Come on, Lily.
It's your time to die now.
-Die!
-[crowd] Kill her!
-Hang her!
-She's a murderer!
[Camila wailing]
[Camia] You monsters! You're all monsters!
-Kill her!
-Just stop this!
Please!
[woman] She killed the mayor. Kill her!
[man] She's a scum! She deserves to die!
-[crowd jeering]
-[Camia crying]
-[Camia] Stop!
-Right! Hang her!
-Yeah, kill her!
-That's what she deserves!
-Hang her!
-Die, Lily!
-Lily… [crying]
-Kill her!
[people chanting] Kill Lily!
[Julio] Citizens of Ardiente!
I present to you Mayor Arnaldo's killer…
-[crowd jeering]
-…Lily Cruz!
-Murderer!
-Scum!
Please, no…
-She's scum!
-Hang her now!
-Execute her!
-Die, murderer!
-Hang her!
-You witch!
-[crowd jeering]
-[Camia wailing]
[Camia] Stop!
Execute her.
-[Emilia clapping]
-[crowd jeering]
Down!
-Kill her!
-Down!
[crowd jeering]
Ready?
-Take her down!
-Kill her!
-Murderer!
-Hang her!
-Lily, my dear…
-[crowd jeering]
-Die!
-Kill her now!
[crowd jeering]
[crowd chanting] Kill her!
Thank you for gathering
the townspeople today!
Papa…
Now they can see…
just how tainted your souls really are!
[camera shutter clicking]
-Diego?
-[man] What?
[suspenseful music playing]
Who are you to talk like that, huh?
Don't believe them!
[Diego] We have proof!
[Edna] Watch this!
We've found the corpses of our loved ones!
And they were killed by the Ardientes!
What they're saying is true!
We were loyal followers
of the Ardientes too,
until we saw the mass grave ourselves!
Witnesses against the Ardientes
have also testified!
[Marlon] The murderous family you idolize
has been exposed to the whole world.
[Fernan] You're the only ones
who remain blind to the truth!
[slow tense music playing]
[camera shutter clicking]
-Down with the Ardientes!
-Down!
-Down with--
-[Anna] Diego?
[Marlon] Diego…
Everyone, help me save my wife
from the Ardientes!
Let's go to the plaza and save Lily!
Diego.
The place is heavily guarded
by the Ardientes' men.
I have a plan.
[Diego] We'll storm the plaza.
We'll use the loyalists they gathered
as shields against them.
We can't face them head-on.
But we'll infiltrate the plaza…
-using these signs and shirts.
-THANK YOU, ARDIENTE.
We'll pose as their allies.
And we'll save Lily Cruz.
[Diego] Our only weapon is the truth.
Jepoy.
We're ready.
We're ready to infiltrate the plaza.
-Is this true?!
-We believed in you!
You fooled us!
You liars!
Silence, all of you!
Don't believe their lies!
They're the criminals!
They're the ones
wreaking havoc in our town!
[Diego] You're the criminals!
You murderers!
-Murderers!
-Bring them down!
[crowd jeering]
Papa…
-You monsters!
-Murderers!
As expected…
you're all idiots!
You should listen to me!
You should follow me!
I'm the King of Ardiente!
What?
Cat got your tongues?
Do you want money?
Fine!
Here's your money! Happy now?
Well?
Have some more!
Viva Ardiente!
-Viva Ardiente!
Viva, Ardiente!
[tense music playing]
Down with the Ardientes!
-Down!
-Down with the Ardientes!
Down!
[crowd chanting] Down with the Ardientes!
[crowd keeps chanting]
Down with the Ardientes!
Down! Down with the Ardientes!
-Magbanua, do something!
-Julio Ardiente, Emilia Torillo!
[crowd] Down!
Surrender now! We have you surrounded!
[tense music playing]
Don't listen to them!
Arrest them! Arrest them--
-[gunshots]
-[shrieks]
-[man] Hold your fire! Hold your fire!
[gunshots]
[Col. Magbanua] Go!
Hold your fire!
-[gunshots]
-[crowd clamoring]
Finally! Serves the Ardientes right!
[Camia] Diego!
-Get down!
-You!
-[gunshots]
-[people clamoring]
You…
[Emilia] Do something!
This is all your fault!
You ruined my family.
You ruined Ardiente.
This is your fault!
[loud thud]
[indistinct screaming]
Diego, save Lily!
Lily!
Papa, let's go!
Lily, my dear!
Don't let the Ardientes get away!
-[crowd clamoring]
-Marlon!
[grunts, groans]
-Lily!
Hurry!
Save her, please…
Hurry, please!
-Put her down!
-Make way!
-Boss!
-Get back!
-Out of the way!
-Slowly now.
-Lily…
Move! Move!
Papa, why did the people turn on us?
-What went wrong? Tell me!
-[faint shouting]
-My God, they're here!
-[loud tapping on windows]
There's no one to blame but Lily Cruz!
-[loud tapping, shouting]
-We should move!
Get us out of here!
-[loud tapping on windows]
-[indistinct shouting]
[Camia sobbing]
Lily…
-Untie her.
-Hold on. Wait. Wait.
-Careful on her head.
-[Camia sobbing]
-[keys clanking]
-[tense music playing]
[panting]
Lily?
-Lily?
-Lily…
[panicked breathing]
Lily…
My dear…
[Camia sobbing]
[somber music playing]
[somber music continues playing]
-Lily!
-Wake up!
Lily, please!
[somber music playing]
-Get up, dear.
-Keep fighting.
You can do it, dear.
Don't give up.
-Lily?
-[Lily coughs]
-Oh, my dear…
-Lily?
-Lily!
-Long live the new Ardiente!
Lily?!
-Long live!
-[crowd chanting] Long live!
-[sobbing]
[cheering and applause]
Long live the new Ardiente!
-Long live!
Long live the new Poblacion Ardiente!
[cheering and applause]
-Long live!
[crowd cheering, applauding]
[somber music playing]
[crowd chanting] New Poblacion Ardiente!
[dramatic music playing]
[metal clanking]
-Pull!
-Go!
-[crowd cheering]
-[echoing thud]
[crowd cheering, applauding]
[dramatic music playing]
[man] Let's celebrate!
[crowd chanting] New Poblacion Ardiente!
[dramatic music playing]
[car honking]
[tense music playing]
-Assist my father.
-[Julio grunting]
[Julio groans]
[tense music playing]
This town…
was made with the flesh
and blood of my ancestors.
Those pathetic ingrates!
They'll have to kill me first
before they kick me out of here!
-Emilia…
-What?
Order a news blackout right away.
No outsider must know
about what happened here today.
[Julio] Come on!
Men, stand your ground.
Don't let anyone in.
[applauding]
-[high-pitched ringing]
-Huh?
-What happened?
-Is it broken?
Melchor, check the antenna.
[Melchor] The TV's working just fine.
I bet this is all Ardiente's doing.
Those crooks!
So, all this time, we've been
supporting liars!
I know.
The Ardientes are murderers.
They're all criminals!
[high-pitched ringing]
There they go again.
Those Ardientes
are stirring up trouble again!
They keep playing us for fools!
You're right!
[phone chimes]
Mom, I got a text message.
Everyone!
Let's pass on Lily Cruz's
message to the others!
The fate of this town is in our hands.
The witnesses against
the Ardientes have come forward.
The secret mass grave has been found.
It's time that the world
learned the truth!
-That's right!
-Yeah!
-Those monsters!
-They lied to us!
-Come on! Let's go!
-Let's go!
[phone chimes]
TOGETHER, LET'S DRIVE
THE ARDIENTES OUT OF THIS TOWN!
Here's a text message.
"Together, let's drive
the Ardientes out of this town!"
-Come on!
-Let's go!
[phone chimes]
TOGETHER, LET'S DRIVE
THE ARDIENTES OUT OF THIS TOWN!
[utensils clanking]
Come on!
Let's get rid of those
Ardientes and restore power
to the townspeople!
-Let's go!
-Come on!
[phones chime]
As you can see, a news blackout
has been declared
in Poblacion Ardiente
where the townspeople have gathered
to overthrow the Ardientes.
I'm doing this because
it's my responsibility
to let the world know
about the real situation
in Poblacion Ardiente.
Please don't bash me.
[suspenseful music playing]
Papa!
Papa, the whole town's coming for us!
[Emilia panting]
Hey! Where are you going?!
I'm packing my things, Papa!
We are not leaving this house!
[foreboding music playing]
Magbanua.
Secure the perimeter.
I don't want any intruders in this house.
Governor, I'm sorry to say this, but
we've lost many of our men.
Most have surrendered, and many are hurt.
I don't give a damn!
Use your bodies as shields if you must.
No one comes into my fortress.
Because this house
is unsinkable.
I am unsinkable!
[tense music playing]
Yes, sir.
-What's the situation?
-Colonel.
Hundreds of people
are heading for the mansion.
They're coming to finish us.
We only have one order from the governor,
and that's to protect the mansion
so no one gets inside.
He has forsaken us.
He doesn't care what happens to us.
We're soldiers.
We're trained to obey, not to question.
Colonel Magbanua,
we've been loyal to you.
But think about us.
We have children.
[crowd clamoring]
Mayday! Mayday! I need backup!
It's getting out of control here!
-Hey! Do you copy?!
-[crowd clamoring]
-I need backup!
The people are forcing their way in--
-[shouting in the distance]
-Men…
Lock and load.
[faint shouting in the distance]
Positions.
Prepare.
[crowd chanting] Down with the Ardientes!
[crowd clamoring]
Men, hold your positions.
Hold!
[suspenseful music playing]
[soldier] Colonel, what are
we going to do?
We can't take them all down.
I don't think we even
have enough bullets, Colonel!
Hold your ground.
Hold your fire.
Hold your fire!
Prepare for maximum tolerance!
-Down with the Ardientes!
-You betrayed us all!
Colonel Magbanua!
Make sure not a single one
of them gets into my house!
Shoot anyone who dares enter!
Kill them all!
Shoot us all you want!
It just proves you're a demon!
May your conscience eat you alive!
-Go on and shoot us!
-Murderer!
Kill them!
The nerve of these peasants
to come here and storm my mansion!
How dare you?!
Colonel!
You have a sworn duty…
to protect me!
Protect me! Shoot them!
Kill them!
-Don't kill us!
-Please, have mercy!
-Spare us!
-Have mercy!
[indistinct cries]
Don't kill us!
[man] Have mercy on us!
[indistinct cries]
Magbanua!
[indistinct crying, yelling]
Why aren't you shooting?!
-Please, don't!
-Don't kill us!
Hold… hold your fire!
-Magbanua!
-Hold!
What the hell are you waiting for?!
-Shoot them!
-Hold!
[man] Go ahead! Shoot us!
-Kill them!
-So the whole world will know…
-Men!
-…how evil you are!
Stand down! Stand down!
Men, stand down!
-Governor…
-Colonel!
-Get inside.
-Thank you, Colonel.
Please!
You fool.
Stand down, men.
[tense music playing]
-[camera shutters clicking]
-[crying]
You filthy little peasants!
You're all worthless!
Is this how you thank your Father Julio?
I'm the one who kept you alive!
If it weren't for me,
you'd have starved to death!
Get out of my sight!
As for the rest of you, Magbanua,
you're nothing but cowards!
Now, get out of my house!
[loud thud]
[tense music playing]
[camera shutters clicking]
[locks clicking]
There's no way they'll catch me alive.
[crowd chanting] Down with the Ardientes!
[dramatic music playing]
[dramatic music continues playing]
[tense music playing]
[tense music continues playing]
-[loud tapping on window]
-[people clamoring]
-[camera shutters clicking]
[slow tense music playing]
[woman 1] Come on!
-Let's find those Ardientes!
-Where are those criminals?
-These thieves.
-Wow. This is so beautiful.
-It's beautiful.
-It's so grand. Incredible!
-My goodness!
-These are beautiful.
[woman 1] These are from
the public's money.
[woman 2] Wow!
Look at all this jewelry!
These are expensive.
They'll look good on me.
-Wow! Incredible!
-Take everything!
-What are you doing?!
-Emilia!
-Put that down!
-Wretched Ardiente!
-Those are mine!
-You thief!
These don't belong to you!
-These are from public funds!
-You're all thieves!
-Give them back!
-You're the thief!
We're taking them back!
-How dare you?!
-How dare you steal my things?!
Hey! You and your family
are the thieves here!
-That's right!
-Move!
-How dare you!
-That's mine!
Give me that!
This is the public's money!
Thief! You want it?
Shove it down your throat!
Have some more! You people are shameless!
[Emilia] You thieves!
-You crook!
-You're the thief!
-[loud tapping on window]
-[people clamoring]
[Julio] Pigs!
Pathetic ingrates!
-[loud tapping on window]
-[people clamoring]
You want a piece of me, huh?!
-[people yelling, shouting]
-Low-lying…
blood-sucking parasites.
That's all you are!
-[people clamoring]
-Papa, thank God!
Enough, Papa!
Enough! We have to go!
The whole house is surrounded!
Let them come in!
So they can all suffer
the wrath of their Father Julio!
I'll kill them all!
No, Papa!
You're going to die here! I'm leaving!
[Julio] Come on!
I'm here! Come on!
Papa, let's go, please?!
Let's go!
-[loud tapping on window]
-[people clamoring]
Ingrates!
Enough! Papa, let's go!
-[loud tapping on window]
-[people clamoring]
Papa, let's go! Come on!
[people yelling, shouting]
[Emilia] Papa, they're coming inside!
Papa! Let's go!
-Down with the Ardientes!
-Down! Down!
-[people clamoring]
-[tense music playing]
All this came from the taxpayers' money!
These are from taxpayers' money!
Take all of them!
-[glass breaking]
-[objects clattering]
-Take them all!
-Go!
They stole this from us!
Take everything!
We're taking back what's ours!
Take it all!
-This is mine!
-Hey!
[woman] That's from taxpayers' money!
Those Ardientes are thieves!
-This one's mine!
-Those monsters!
Stop it!
[indistinct shouting]
[Emilia] They're taking my picture, Papa!
It's over! Let's go, Papa!
[Julio] Don't touch my daughter's picture!
-Leave that picture alone!
-[loud thud]
[Emilia] Pa, they ruined
everything. It's over!
It's over!
Julio Ardiente, you monster!
-[loud smashing]
-[people yelling]
-[Julio] Bastards!
-[Emilia crying]
-[loud smashing, crashing]
-[indistinct shouting]
You bastards!
-[gunshots]
-[Emilia screaming] Papa!
-Papa, enough! Papa!
-[gunshots]
[Julio] You animals!
-Papa, enough!
Enough! Enough!
Papa! Enough!
Enough!
-[indistinct yelling]
-[dramatic music playing]
[Emilia] Let's go!
[people clamoring]
[people chanting] Down with the Ardientes!
THE ARDIENTES ARE EVIL!
-Down with the Ardientes!
-[loud smashing, breaking]
-[people clamoring]
-[dramatic music playing]
[Julio] I never thought
it would come to this.
That a single wildflower
would take down a king like me.
[Leandro] Our town's true
and rightful governor,
Diego Torillo!
[crowd] Diego! Diego! Diego!
-[Lily] You are my life, Diego.
-I love you so much.
[Lily] I love you so much too, Diego.
[Diego] We will wipe away
all the filth left in our town.
And together, we will create…
-…a new Poblacion Ardiente!
-Diego! Diego!
[gunshot]
[people clamoring]
[theme music playing]